joerogan.net 2008-05-16

# Joe Rogan

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to JoeRogan.net and its subsidiaries. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices. We do not sell, rent, or loan any personal information (any information from which you can be identified) regarding our users to anyone outside of JoeRogan.net. Any information you give us is treated with care, subject to this Privacy Policy, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. 

**The Information We Collect**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web Site ("Site"), and to gather broad demographic information using a standard Site statistics software package. 

**Information Submitted to Us**  
When you submit information to us, for example, by using the web-based form submission, file uploads (including resumes) or one of the e-mail links, provided on our Site, we will attempt to respond to your request. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security**  
We use reasonable industry standard technology to keep information that you submit to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot warrant the security of any information transmitted to us and you do so at your own risk. 

**Your Consent**  
We value your privacy; however, at all times we reserve the right to disclose information, where required by law, to comply with valid legal processes such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; to protect JoeRogan.net's rights and property; or during emergencies when safety is at risk. 

By using this Site, you agree that we may collect and use information for the purposes for which the information was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not access this Site. Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our Privacy Policy. Your continued accessing of JoeRogan.net’s Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept and agree to be bound by such changes. 

**Use of Third Party Opt-in Lists**  
With respect to JoeRogan.net’s use of third party opt-in lists, JoeRogan.net may enter into co-branding arrangements with other companies, and if so, an opt-in question may be present for contact from these organizations as well. The opt-in features are specific to each organization, but you should never receive e-mail from these organizations unless you have indicated that it is acceptable. All e-mail from JoeRogan.net, or from co-brand partners who gain your permission to send you commercial e-mail, will include an opportunity to opt-out of future communications. 

**Inquiries**  
If you have any comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, please click here to send us an email.
